<head>
<h1> A Beginner's Guide to Eudora Lite for Windows
<body> This is a beginner's guide to using Eudora Lite 1.5.4 for Windows 95. It covers everything you 
need to know to start using Eudora to send and receive e-mail, including: (1) essential settings 
and program configuration; (2) the basic tasks involved in composing and sending e-mail, 
receiving and reading messages, as well as what to do with them when your done; and (3) how to 
find more information about using Eudora once 
you've learned the basics. 
<p>Eudora Lite is freeware (software which may be used at no cost) that offers a set of tools and basic e-mail utilities for managing electronic mail messages. The program employs standard 
 Windows graphical interface elements, so that anyone familiar with the Windows environment 
should find Eudora easy to navigate. The application is configured to access a specific account 
on a POP server—a computer connected to a network or the Internet running software that sends, 
receives and stores e-mail. Eudora then acts as the communication agent between the remote 
server and the local computer—sending and receiving mail messages to and from the POP account. Finally, Eudora offers a set of utilities for manipulating and organizing messages sto
red on the local system.</p> 
<p>To use this guide you need only be familiar with the basics of mouse operation and navigating 
standard Windows interface objects such as menus, windows, dialog boxes, and toolbars.</p> 
<h2>Eudora Setup</h2>
<p>Before you can begin using Eudora, you must make sure you have the right equipment and 
configure Eudora. </p>
<p>Getting started. To use these instructions, you'll need the following: An IBM PC
-
compatible computer running under Windows 95. 
•
A copy of the Eudora 
Lite application installed and currently running on your machine. 
•
Internet access with a POP3 e
-
mail account. 
Note:
If you are not sure what kind of account you have, contact your Internet Service 
Provider. POP simply refers to the type of software used 
on the remote server where your 
e
-
mail is received and stored. Most e
-
mail accounts today use POP3 software. </p>
<p>Before you can use Eudora for completing basic e
-
mail tasks, you must tell the program a few 
things about yourself and your account. If Eudora is 
not running, you should start it now. </p>
</head>